Turned it on after all these years
오랜만에 전원을 켰어.
Dust on the cartridge dust on the screen
카트리지에도 화면에도 먼지.
Three empty slots where stories lived
이야기가 살았던 세 개의 빈 슬롯.
Like someone erased a dream
마치 누군가 꿈을 지운 듯이.
But the cursor blinks on slot one
하지만 커서는 슬롯 1번에서 깜빡여.
And it whispers something new
그리고 무언가 새로운 걸 속삭여.
Start again from nothing
아무것도 없는 곳에서 다시 시작해.
Every blank page holds a song
모든 빈 페이지엔 노래가 담겨 있어.
All the maps are waiting
모든 지도가 기다리고 있어.
Undrawn worlds where I belong
내가 속할 그려지지 않은 세상.
Hundred hours gone without a trace
수백 시간이 흔적도 없이 사라졌어.
No saved princess no final score
구한 공주도 없고 최종 점수도 없어.
But my hands still know the buttons
하지만 내 손은 아직 버튼들을 기억해.
And the music plays once more
그리고 음악이 다시 한번 흘러.
So the cursor blinks on slot one
그래서 커서는 슬롯 1번에서 깜빡여.
And I press it knowing now
그리고 이제는 알기에 그걸 눌러.
Start again from nothing
아무것도 없는 곳에서 다시 시작해.
Every blank page holds a song
모든 빈 페이지엔 노래가 담겨 있어.
All the maps are waiting
모든 지도가 기다리고 있어.
Undrawn worlds where I belong
내가 속할 그려지지 않은 세상.
Start again from nothing
아무것도 없는 곳에서 다시 시작해.
Every blank page holds a song
모든 빈 페이지엔 노래가 담겨 있어.
All the maps are waiting
모든 지도가 기다리고 있어.
Undrawn worlds where I belong
내가 속할 그려지지 않은 세상.